Thank you. Your next question comes from the line of Emmanuel Papadakis from Deutsche Bank.
Please go ahead. Thank you for taking the question. Maybe I'll take one on Iron Alamad
and Sjogren's. Given we must be relatively late in the regulatory review process, could you perhaps
just give us an update on how that's proceeding? Is everything on track? And are you expecting a
panel? And then on commercial readiness, some sense of expectations for magnitude of initial
access, breadth and willingness to prescribe, et cetera. Could you just give us a sense in
those parameters? Should we be looking at something like classic immunology launch like
Cosimta?
Thanks, Emmanuel. So again, as far as we know, no advisory committee plan for
Iron Alamad. We've had them in cycle review meetings. And so we're continuing to provide
FDA all the information they're requesting. So all on track from that point for a Q3 approval.
I think from a market uptake standpoint, our current expectation is given that there's no
approved therapy in Sjogren's, we should get relatively, you know, broad access with all the
caveats that this does take time to get the environment opened up. And then we think that
physicians, given that the drug has a clean safety profile, will err on the side of trialing
the drug in patients and ultimately seeing how patients respond. I mean, this is a very
heterogeneous patient population. Even the STI endpoint is covering a broad range of domains.
And we do see in our own...
In our own data sets, there are patients who are super responders and patients who respond less well.
And so we're, I think, going to see in the marketplace, you know, for patients who respond,
they'll stay on medicine and other patients will cycle off. But I think the key thing here is we
have a clean safety profile, which lowers the, I think, bar for physicians to at least give patients
the option, given the nature of disease. These are young, often young female patients in working age
who obviously want better control of their symptoms and their disease. So we're optimistic
on that front as well. We continue to guide that standalone in Sjogren's, we should reach
a multi-billion dollar potential. And then, as I mentioned in my opening comments,
Enalimab has a number of other indications that we're also pursuing both in hematology
and in immunology.